{
    "subject": "resource/Kickapoo_Joy_Juice",
    "predicate": "ontology/origin",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Kickapoo Joy Juice originated from the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.938387930393219,
            "question": "Is Kickapoo Joy Juice a product of the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9336331486701965,
            "question": "Where did Kickapoo Joy Juice originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8883562684059143,
            "question": "What country is associated with the origin of Kickapoo Joy Juice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7347967028617859,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the history of Kickapoo Joy Juice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5591064691543579,
            "question": "Is Kickapoo Joy Juice a popular beverage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5098225474357605,
            "question": "Is there a specific brand associated with Kickapoo Joy Juice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4869621694087982,
            "question": "Where can you typically find Kickapoo Joy Juice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42068618535995483,
            "question": "Are there any unique characteristics of Kickapoo Joy Juice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4076851010322571,
            "question": "What type of product is Kickapoo Joy Juice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3361242413520813,
            "question": "What is the flavor profile of Kickapoo Joy Juice?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kickapoo Joy Juice originated from the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8220_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of product is Kickapoo Joy Juice?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8220_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any unique characteristics of Kickapoo Joy Juice?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8220_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you typically find Kickapoo Joy Juice?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8220_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8220_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8220_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8220_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8220_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8220_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8220_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8220_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8220_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8220_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8220_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nThe documents state that Kickapoo Joy Juice was first introduced in the United States in 1965, but it originated from the comic strip \"Li'l Abner,\" which is not based in the United States.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The original source of Kickapoo Joy Juice is mentioned as \"Li'l Abner\", an American comic strip.\n* However, it's also mentioned that the real-world beverage was launched in the United States in 1965, which might suggest a connection to the US.\n\nConsidering these points, I would say that the information in the documents partially supports the triple. There is some evidence that suggests Kickapoo Joy Juice has a connection to the United States, but it's not clear if it originated there or was simply launched there later on.\n\nSo, my response would be:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"maybe\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that \"Kickapoo Joy Juice\" was introduced in the United States in 1965 and is currently popular in markets such as Malaysia and Singapore, suggesting its origin in the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n\nThe documents provided indicate that the concept of Kickapoo Joy Juice was introduced through Li\u2019l Abner, an American comic strip. Furthermore, the real-life version of Kickapoo Joy Juice debuted in the United States in 1965 and was based on this comic strip which ran from the 1930s to the 1970s. Therefore, it is accurate to say that Kickapoo Joy Juice originated from the United States."
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Kickapoo Joy Juice was a joint venture between Malaysia and the United States.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "It explicitly states in the context information that Kickapoo Joy Juice was based on the newspaper comic strip \"Li'l Abner,\" which launched in the 1930s, and that the real-life version of the drink debuted in the United States in 1965.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}